[
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé is 92,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé has a mileage of 125 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé has Moteur 136 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.2L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 4 Gran Coupé?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/191/BMWS%C3%A9rie4GranCoup%C3%A9."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Opel Combo Cargo?",
        "answer": "The price of the Opel Combo Cargo is 65,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Opel Combo Cargo?",
        "answer": "The Opel Combo Cargo has a mileage of 750 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Opel Combo Cargo use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Opel Combo Cargo have?",
        "answer": "The Opel Combo Cargo has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Opel Combo Cargo?",
        "answer": "The Opel Combo Cargo has Moteur 92 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Opel Combo Cargo?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.8 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Opel Combo Cargo come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Opel Combo Cargo?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Opel Combo Cargo?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/190/OpelComboCargo."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes CLA 180?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes CLA 180 is 69,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes CLA 180?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes CLA 180 has a mileage of 131 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes CLA 180 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes CLA 180 have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes CLA 180 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes CLA 180?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes CLA 180 has Moteur 122 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes CLA 180?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.6 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes CLA 180 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes CLA 180?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes CLA 180?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/189/MercedesCLA180."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "The price of the Suzuki Vitara is 62,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "The Suzuki Vitara has a mileage of 68 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Suzuki Vitara use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Suzuki Vitara have?",
        "answer": "The Suzuki Vitara has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "The Suzuki Vitara has Moteur 120 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.7 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Suzuki Vitara come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/188/suzukiVitara."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi A5 S-line Quattro?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi A5 S-line Quattro is 68,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi A5 S-line Quattro?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line Quattro has a mileage of 258 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi A5 S-line Quattro use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi A5 S-line Quattro have?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line Quattro has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi A5 S-line Quattro?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line Quattro has Moteur 211 cv and Puissance Fiscale 12 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi A5 S-line Quattro?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.4L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi A5 S-line Quattro come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi A5 S-line Quattro?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi A5 S-line Quattro?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/187/AudiA5S-line."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "The price of the Nissan Qashqai is 71,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "The Nissan Qashqai has a mileage of 149 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Nissan Qashqai use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Nissan Qashqai have?",
        "answer": "The Nissan Qashqai has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "The Nissan Qashqai has Moteur 115 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.8 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Nissan Qashqai come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/186/NissanQashqai."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi A4 35 TFSI?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi A4 35 TFSI is 119,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi A4 35 TFSI?",
        "answer": "The Audi A4 35 TFSI has a mileage of 29 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi A4 35 TFSI use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi A4 35 TFSI have?",
        "answer": "The Audi A4 35 TFSI has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi A4 35 TFSI?",
        "answer": "The Audi A4 35 TFSI has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi A4 35 TFSI?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 8.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi A4 35 TFSI come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi A4 35 TFSI?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi A4 35 TFSI?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/185/AudiA435TFSI."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes Classe E180?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes Classe E180 is 115,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes Classe E180?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe E180 has a mileage of 148 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes Classe E180 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes Classe E180 have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe E180 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes Classe E180?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe E180 has Moteur 156 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes Classe E180?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 8.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes Classe E180 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes Classe E180?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Palettes au volant Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes Classe E180?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/184/MercedesClasseE180."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi A5 S-line is 140,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line has a mileage of 94 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi A5 S-line use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi A5 S-line have?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.1 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi A5 S-line come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/182/AudiA5S-line."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Honda CR-V?",
        "answer": "The price of the Honda CR-V is 105,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Honda CR-V?",
        "answer": "The Honda CR-V has a mileage of 110 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Honda CR-V use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Honda CR-V have?",
        "answer": "The Honda CR-V has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Honda CR-V?",
        "answer": "The Honda CR-V has Moteur 193 cv and Puissance Fiscale 11 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Honda CR-V?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.1 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Honda CR-V come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Honda CR-V?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Honda CR-V?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/181/HondaCR-V."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Wallyscar 719?",
        "answer": "The price of the Wallyscar 719 is 42,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Wallyscar 719?",
        "answer": "The Wallyscar 719 has a mileage of 7 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Wallyscar 719 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Wallyscar 719 have?",
        "answer": "The Wallyscar 719 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Wallyscar 719?",
        "answer": "The Wallyscar 719 has Moteur 115 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Wallyscar 719?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.1 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Wallyscar 719 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Wallyscar 719?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Wallyscar 719?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/180/Wallyscar719."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford Focus Titanium?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford Focus Titanium is 38,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford Focus Titanium?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus Titanium has a mileage of 192 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford Focus Titanium use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford Focus Titanium have?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus Titanium has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford Focus Titanium?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus Titanium has Moteur 125 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford Focus Titanium?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.9 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford Focus Titanium come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford Focus Titanium?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford Focus Titanium?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/179/FordFocusTitanium."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Honda Civic?",
        "answer": "The price of the Honda Civic is 77,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Honda Civic?",
        "answer": "The Honda Civic has a mileage of 159 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Honda Civic use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Honda Civic have?",
        "answer": "The Honda Civic has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Honda Civic?",
        "answer": "The Honda Civic has Moteur 182 cv and Puissance Fiscale 10 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Honda Civic?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.1 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Honda Civic come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Honda Civic?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Honda Civic?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/177/HondaCivic."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Volkswagen Tiguan R Line?",
        "answer": "The price of the Volkswagen Tiguan R Line is 177,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Volkswagen Tiguan R Line?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan R Line has a mileage of 6 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Volkswagen Tiguan R Line use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Volkswagen Tiguan R Line have?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan R Line has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Volkswagen Tiguan R Line?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan R Line has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Volkswagen Tiguan R Line?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.7 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Volkswagen Tiguan R Line come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Volkswagen Tiguan R Line?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Volkswagen Tiguan R Line?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/176/VolkswagenTiguanRLine."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 2?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 2 is 115,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 2?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 2 has a mileage of 52 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 2 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 2 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 2 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 2?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 2 has Moteur 136 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 2?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.1 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 2 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 2?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Palettes au volant Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 2?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/175/BMWS%C3%A9rie2."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The price of the Kia Rio is 62,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has a mileage of 53 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Kia Rio use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Kia Rio have?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has Moteur 84 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Kia Rio come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/174/KiaRio."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "The price of the Peugeot 2008 is 37,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 2008 has a mileage of 136 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Peugeot 2008 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Peugeot 2008 have?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 2008 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 2008 has Moteur 110 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Peugeot 2008 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/173/Peugeot2008."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Porsche Panamera?",
        "answer": "The price of the Porsche Panamera is 170,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Porsche Panamera?",
        "answer": "The Porsche Panamera has a mileage of 56 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Porsche Panamera use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Porsche Panamera have?",
        "answer": "The Porsche Panamera has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Porsche Panamera?",
        "answer": "The Porsche Panamera has Moteur 250 cv and Puissance Fiscale 15 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Porsche Panamera?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.3L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Porsche Panamera come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Porsche Panamera?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Palettes au volant Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Porsche Panamera?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/172/PorschePanamera."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford EcoSport is 69,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has a mileage of 29 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford EcoSport use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford EcoSport have?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has Moteur 125 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford EcoSport come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/171/FordEcoSport."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "The price of the Volkswagen Golf 7 is 56,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Golf 7 has a mileage of 109 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Volkswagen Golf 7 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Volkswagen Golf 7 have?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Golf 7 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Golf 7 has Moteur 105 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Volkswagen Golf 7 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/170/VolkswagenGolf7."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "The price of the Haval H6 is 74,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "The Haval H6 has a mileage of 133 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Haval H6 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Haval H6 have?",
        "answer": "The Haval H6 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "The Haval H6 has Moteur 143 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 9.1 L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Haval H6 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Haval H6?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/169/HavalH6."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The price of the Renault Clio is 98,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has a mileage of 6 100 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Renault Clio use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Hybride as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Renault Clio have?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has Moteur 145 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.2 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Renault Clio come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/167/RenaultClio."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The price of the Renault Clio is 98,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has a mileage of 5 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Renault Clio use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Hybride as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Renault Clio have?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has Moteur 145 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.2 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Renault Clio come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/164/RenaultClio."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Seat Ibiza?",
        "answer": "The price of the Seat Ibiza is 43,200 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Seat Ibiza?",
        "answer": "The Seat Ibiza has a mileage of 132 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Seat Ibiza use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Seat Ibiza have?",
        "answer": "The Seat Ibiza has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Seat Ibiza?",
        "answer": "The Seat Ibiza has Moteur 80 cv and Puissance Fiscale 4 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Seat Ibiza?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Seat Ibiza come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Seat Ibiza?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Port USB Vitres électrique Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Seat Ibiza?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/163/SeatIbiza."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes CLA 250e?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes CLA 250e is 162,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes CLA 250e?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes CLA 250e has a mileage of 49 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes CLA 250e use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Hybride as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes CLA 250e have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes CLA 250e has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes CLA 250e?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes CLA 250e has Moteur 218 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes CLA 250e?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 0.9 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes CLA 250e come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes CLA 250e?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Palettes au volant Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes CLA 250e?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/162/MercedesCLA250e."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Seat Leon?",
        "answer": "The price of the Seat Leon is 47,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Seat Leon?",
        "answer": "The Seat Leon has a mileage of 177 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Seat Leon use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Seat Leon have?",
        "answer": "The Seat Leon has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Seat Leon?",
        "answer": "The Seat Leon has Moteur 110 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Seat Leon?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.1 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Seat Leon come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Seat Leon?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Limiteur de vitesse Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Seat Leon?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/161/SeatLeon."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Great Wall M4?",
        "answer": "The price of the Great Wall M4 is 39,800 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Great Wall M4?",
        "answer": "The Great Wall M4 has a mileage of 99 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Great Wall M4 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Great Wall M4 have?",
        "answer": "The Great Wall M4 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Great Wall M4?",
        "answer": "The Great Wall M4 has Moteur 94 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Great Wall M4?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Great Wall M4 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Great Wall M4?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Great Wall M4?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/160/GreatWallM4."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford Mustang?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford Mustang is 160,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford Mustang?",
        "answer": "The Ford Mustang has a mileage of 57 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford Mustang use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford Mustang have?",
        "answer": "The Ford Mustang has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford Mustang?",
        "answer": "The Ford Mustang has Moteur 317cv and Puissance Fiscale 21 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford Mustang?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 8 L/100 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford Mustang come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford Mustang?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Limiteur de vitesse Palettes au volant Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford Mustang?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/159/FordMustang."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of MG ZS?",
        "answer": "The price of the MG ZS is 77,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of MG ZS?",
        "answer": "The MG ZS has a mileage of 23 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the MG ZS use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the MG ZS have?",
        "answer": "The MG ZS has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of MG ZS?",
        "answer": "The MG ZS has Moteur 114 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of MG ZS?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the MG ZS come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of MG ZS?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about MG ZS?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/158/MGZS."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Chery Tiggo 3X?",
        "answer": "The price of the Chery Tiggo 3X is 54,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Chery Tiggo 3X?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 3X has a mileage of 62 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Chery Tiggo 3X use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Chery Tiggo 3X have?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 3X has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Chery Tiggo 3X?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 3X has Moteur 102 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Chery Tiggo 3X?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.9 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Chery Tiggo 3X come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Chery Tiggo 3X?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Chery Tiggo 3X?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/157/CheryTiggo3X."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford EcoSport is 66,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has a mileage of 77 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford EcoSport use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford EcoSport have?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has Moteur 125 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.1 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford EcoSport come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Sonorisation Bang and Olufsen Palettes au volant Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/146/FordEcoSport."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi A3 is 64,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "The Audi A3 has a mileage of 154 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi A3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi A3 have?",
        "answer": "The Audi A3 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "The Audi A3 has Moteur 110 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi A3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi A3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/145/AudiA3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Seat Arona?",
        "answer": "The price of the Seat Arona is 75,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Seat Arona?",
        "answer": "The Seat Arona has a mileage of 43 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Seat Arona use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Seat Arona have?",
        "answer": "The Seat Arona has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Seat Arona?",
        "answer": "The Seat Arona has Moteur 115 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Seat Arona?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Seat Arona come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Seat Arona?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Seat Arona?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/143/SeatArona."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "The price of the Nissan Qashqai is 37,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "The Nissan Qashqai has a mileage of 228 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Nissan Qashqai use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Nissan Qashqai have?",
        "answer": "The Nissan Qashqai has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "The Nissan Qashqai has Moteur 106 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.1 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Nissan Qashqai come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Toit ouvrant panoramique Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Nissan Qashqai?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/142/NissanQashqai."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Haval Jolion?",
        "answer": "The price of the Haval Jolion is 84,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Haval Jolion?",
        "answer": "The Haval Jolion has a mileage of 35 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Haval Jolion use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Haval Jolion have?",
        "answer": "The Haval Jolion has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Haval Jolion?",
        "answer": "The Haval Jolion has Moteur 143 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Haval Jolion?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Haval Jolion come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Haval Jolion?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Haval Jolion?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/141/HavalJolion."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Renault Clio Tce?",
        "answer": "The price of the Renault Clio Tce is 41,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Renault Clio Tce?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio Tce has a mileage of 122 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Renault Clio Tce use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Renault Clio Tce have?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio Tce has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Renault Clio Tce?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio Tce has Moteur 90 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Renault Clio Tce?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.2 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Renault Clio Tce come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Renault Clio Tce?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Climatisation."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Renault Clio Tce?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/137/RenaultClioTce."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi A5 S-line is 125,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line has a mileage of 104 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi A5 S-line use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi A5 S-line have?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "The Audi A5 S-line has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.1 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi A5 S-line come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi A5 S-line?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/135/AudiA5S-line."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Land Rover Discovery?",
        "answer": "The price of the Land Rover Discovery is 114,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Land Rover Discovery?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Discovery has a mileage of 176 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Land Rover Discovery use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Land Rover Discovery have?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Discovery has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Land Rover Discovery?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Discovery has Moteur 240 cv and Puissance Fiscale 15."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Land Rover Discovery?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Land Rover Discovery come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Land Rover Discovery?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Land Rover Discovery?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/133/LandRoverDiscovery."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW X1?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW X1 is 175,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW X1?",
        "answer": "The BMW X1 has a mileage of 21 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW X1 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW X1 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW X1 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW X1?",
        "answer": "The BMW X1 has Moteur 156 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW X1?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.9 L/100."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW X1 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW X1?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW X1?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/132/BMWX1."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW X5?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW X5 is 170,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW X5?",
        "answer": "The BMW X5 has a mileage of 214 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW X5 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW X5 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW X5 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW X5?",
        "answer": "The BMW X5 has Moteur 231 cv and Puissance Fiscale 13 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW X5?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.3 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW X5 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW X5?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Caméra 360⁰ Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW X5?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/130/BMWX5."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes classe C is 90,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes classe C has a mileage of 176 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes classe C use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes classe C have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes classe C has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes classe C has Moteur 156 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.6 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes classe C come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/128/MercedesclasseC."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi A3 is 119,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "The Audi A3 has a mileage of 56 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi A3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi A3 have?",
        "answer": "The Audi A3 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "The Audi A3 has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.6 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi A3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi A3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi A3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/127/AudiA3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Jaguar XJL?",
        "answer": "The price of the Jaguar XJL is 150,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Jaguar XJL?",
        "answer": "The Jaguar XJL has a mileage of 51 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Jaguar XJL use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Jaguar XJL have?",
        "answer": "The Jaguar XJL has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Jaguar XJL?",
        "answer": "The Jaguar XJL has Moteur 240 cv and Puissance Fiscale 16 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Jaguar XJL?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 9.3 l/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Jaguar XJL come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Jaguar XJL?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Jaguar XJL?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/125/JaguarXJL."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi A7?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi A7 is 295,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi A7?",
        "answer": "The Audi A7 has a mileage of 86 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi A7 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi A7 have?",
        "answer": "The Audi A7 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi A7?",
        "answer": "The Audi A7 has Moteur 330 cv and Puissance Fiscale 23 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi A7?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi A7 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi A7?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi A7?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/117/AudiA7."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "The price of the Kia sportage is 95,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "The Kia sportage has a mileage of 61 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Kia sportage use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Kia sportage have?",
        "answer": "The Kia sportage has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "The Kia sportage has Moteur 132 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Kia sportage come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/116/Kiasportage."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes GLC Coupé?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes GLC Coupé is 245,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes GLC Coupé?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLC Coupé has a mileage of 70 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes GLC Coupé use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Hybride as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes GLC Coupé have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLC Coupé has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes GLC Coupé?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLC Coupé has Moteur 211 cv and Puissance Fiscale 12 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes GLC Coupé?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.2 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes GLC Coupé come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes GLC Coupé?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes GLC Coupé?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/115/MercedesGLCcoupe."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes Classe A is 137,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe A has a mileage of 35 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes Classe A use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Hybride as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes Classe A have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe A has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe A has Moteur 218 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 1.5L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes Classe A come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Android Auto Apple Car Play Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/114/MercedesClasseA."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 4 Coupé?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 4 Coupé is 265,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 4 Coupé?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 Coupé has a mileage of 20 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 4 Coupé use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 4 Coupé have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 Coupé has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 4 Coupé?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 Coupé has Moteur 184 cv and Puissance Fiscale 10 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 4 Coupé?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.6 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 4 Coupé come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 4 Coupé?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Android Auto Apple Car Play Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 4 Coupé?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/110/BMWSerie4Coupe."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Hyundai Tucson?",
        "answer": "The price of the Hyundai Tucson is 142,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Hyundai Tucson?",
        "answer": "The Hyundai Tucson has a mileage of 11 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Hyundai Tucson use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Hyundai Tucson have?",
        "answer": "The Hyundai Tucson has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Hyundai Tucson?",
        "answer": "The Hyundai Tucson has Moteur 180 ch and Puissance Fiscale 10 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Hyundai Tucson?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.3L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Hyundai Tucson come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Hyundai Tucson?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Hyundai Tucson?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/108/HyundaiTucson."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "The price of the Land Rover Range Rover is 460,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Range Rover has a mileage of 52 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Land Rover Range Rover use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Land Rover Range Rover have?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Range Rover has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Range Rover has Moteur 510 cv and Puissance Fiscale 43 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 12.8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Land Rover Range Rover come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/106/LANDROVERRANGEROVER."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes GLC 220?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes GLC 220 is 220,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes GLC 220?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLC 220 has a mileage of 39 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes GLC 220 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes GLC 220 have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLC 220 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes GLC 220?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLC 220 has Moteur 170 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes GLC 220?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes GLC 220 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes GLC 220?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes GLC 220?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/103/MercedesGLC220."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Chery Tiggo 8?",
        "answer": "The price of the Chery Tiggo 8 is 88,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Chery Tiggo 8?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 8 has a mileage of 49 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Chery Tiggo 8 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Chery Tiggo 8 have?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 8 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Chery Tiggo 8?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 8 has Moteur 154 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Chery Tiggo 8?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Chery Tiggo 8 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Chery Tiggo 8?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Chery Tiggo 8?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/100/CheryTiggo8."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "The price of the Land Rover Range Rover is 145,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Range Rover has a mileage of 178 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Land Rover Range Rover use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Land Rover Range Rover have?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Range Rover has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "The Land Rover Range Rover has Moteur 256 cv and Puissance Fiscale 17 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Land Rover Range Rover come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Land Rover Range Rover?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/99/LANDROVERRANGEROVERSPORT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Porsche Macan?",
        "answer": "The price of the Porsche Macan is 360,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Porsche Macan?",
        "answer": "The Porsche Macan has a mileage of 22 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Porsche Macan use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Porsche Macan have?",
        "answer": "The Porsche Macan has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Porsche Macan?",
        "answer": "The Porsche Macan has Moteur 265 cv and Puissance Fiscale 17 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Porsche Macan?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 9.3 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Porsche Macan come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Porsche Macan?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Porsche Macan?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/97/PorscheMacan."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 1 is 80,800 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 1 has a mileage of 111 074 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 1 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 1 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 1 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 1 has Moteur 136 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6 L /100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 1 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/96/BmwSerie1."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Hyundai Creta?",
        "answer": "The price of the Hyundai Creta is 74,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Hyundai Creta?",
        "answer": "The Hyundai Creta has a mileage of 90 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Hyundai Creta use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Hyundai Creta have?",
        "answer": "The Hyundai Creta has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Hyundai Creta?",
        "answer": "The Hyundai Creta has Moteur 113 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Hyundai Creta?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.1 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Hyundai Creta come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Hyundai Creta?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Hyundai Creta?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/94/HyundaiCreta."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW X4?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW X4 is 243,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW X4?",
        "answer": "The BMW X4 has a mileage of 50 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW X4 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW X4 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW X4 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW X4?",
        "answer": "The BMW X4 has Moteur 184 cv and Puissance Fiscale 11 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW X4?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW X4 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW X4?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW X4?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/93/BMWX4."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW X2 is 132,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "The BMW X2 has a mileage of 38 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW X2 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW X2 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW X2 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "The BMW X2 has Moteur 140 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW X2 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW X2?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/92/BMWX2."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 4 is 97,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 has a mileage of 108 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 4 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 4 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 has Moteur 136 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.2L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 4 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/91/BMWS%C3%A9rie4."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of MG HS?",
        "answer": "The price of the MG HS is 77,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of MG HS?",
        "answer": "The MG HS has a mileage of 78 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the MG HS use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the MG HS have?",
        "answer": "The MG HS has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of MG HS?",
        "answer": "The MG HS has Moteur 162 cv and Puissance Fiscale 10 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of MG HS?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.9 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the MG HS come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of MG HS?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about MG HS?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/88/MGHS."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford Kuga?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford Kuga is 71,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford Kuga?",
        "answer": "The Ford Kuga has a mileage of 93 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford Kuga use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford Kuga have?",
        "answer": "The Ford Kuga has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford Kuga?",
        "answer": "The Ford Kuga has Moteur 120 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford Kuga?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.6 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford Kuga come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford Kuga?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford Kuga?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/85/FordKuga."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "The price of the Volkswagen Golf 7 is 62,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Golf 7 has a mileage of 98 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Volkswagen Golf 7 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Volkswagen Golf 7 have?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Golf 7 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Golf 7 has Moteur 110 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Volkswagen Golf 7 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Volkswagen Golf 7?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/84/VolkswagenGolf7."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "The price of the Kia sportage is 103,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "The Kia sportage has a mileage of 85 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Kia sportage use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Kia sportage have?",
        "answer": "The Kia sportage has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "The Kia sportage has Moteur 132 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Kia sportage come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Kia sportage?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/83/Kiasportage."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford Focus is 37,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus has a mileage of 146 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford Focus use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford Focus have?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus has Moteur 125 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.7 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford Focus come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Radar de recul Climatisation."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/80/FordFocus."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mazda 3?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mazda 3 is 46,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mazda 3?",
        "answer": "The Mazda 3 has a mileage of 133 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mazda 3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mazda 3 have?",
        "answer": "The Mazda 3 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mazda 3?",
        "answer": "The Mazda 3 has Moteur 120 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mazda 3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.1 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mazda 3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mazda 3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mazda 3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/73/Mazda3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes Classe C?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes Classe C is 215,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes Classe C?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe C has a mileage of 35 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes Classe C use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes Classe C have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe C has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes Classe C?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe C has Moteur 193 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes Classe C?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.2 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes Classe C come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes Classe C?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes Classe C?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/72/MercedesClasseC."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "The price of the Haval H6 is 72,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "The Haval H6 has a mileage of 99 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Haval H6 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Haval H6 have?",
        "answer": "The Haval H6 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "The Haval H6 has Moteur 143 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 9.1 L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Haval H6 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Haval H6?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Haval H6?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/71/HavalH6."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford EcoSport is 66,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has a mileage of 94 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford EcoSport use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford EcoSport have?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "The Ford EcoSport has Moteur 125 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.1 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford EcoSport come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Android Auto Apple Car Play Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford EcoSport?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/69/FordEcoSport."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes GLA is 182,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA has a mileage of 91 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes GLA use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes GLA have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA has Moteur 163 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes GLA come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/57/MercedesGLA."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "The price of the Volkswagen Tiguan is 38,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan has a mileage of 209 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Volkswagen Tiguan use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Volkswagen Tiguan have?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan has Moteur 200cv and Puissance Fiscale 11 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 8.5 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Volkswagen Tiguan come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/183/VolkswagenTiguan."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Lada Niva 4*4?",
        "answer": "The price of the Lada Niva 4*4 is 27,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Lada Niva 4*4?",
        "answer": "The Lada Niva 4*4 has a mileage of 89 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Lada Niva 4*4 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Lada Niva 4*4 have?",
        "answer": "The Lada Niva 4*4 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Lada Niva 4*4?",
        "answer": "The Lada Niva 4*4 has Moteur 83 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Lada Niva 4*4?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 9.1 L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Lada Niva 4*4 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Lada Niva 4*4?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Climatisation."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Lada Niva 4*4?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/178/LadaNiva4*4."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "The price of the Volkswagen Tiguan is 68,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan has a mileage of 184 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Volkswagen Tiguan use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Volkswagen Tiguan have?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Tiguan has Moteur 110 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Volkswagen Tiguan come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Régulateur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Volkswagen Tiguan?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/168/VolkswagenTiguan."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mazda 2?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mazda 2 is 36,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mazda 2?",
        "answer": "The Mazda 2 has a mileage of 142 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mazda 2 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mazda 2 have?",
        "answer": "The Mazda 2 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mazda 2?",
        "answer": "The Mazda 2 has Moteur 115 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mazda 2?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.9 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mazda 2 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mazda 2?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mazda 2?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/156/Mazda2."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mini One?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mini One is 35,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mini One?",
        "answer": "The Mini One has a mileage of 125 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mini One use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mini One have?",
        "answer": "The Mini One has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mini One?",
        "answer": "The Mini One has Moteur 75 cv and Puissance Fiscale 4 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mini One?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mini One come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mini One?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mini One?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/155/MiniOne."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 3?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 3 is 66,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 3?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 3 has a mileage of 131 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 3 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 3 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 3?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 3 has Moteur 136 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.9 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/154/BMWS%C3%A9rie3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Serie 3 is 74,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "The BMW Serie 3 has a mileage of 142 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Serie 3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Serie 3 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Serie 3 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "The BMW Serie 3 has Moteur 136 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Serie 3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/152/BMWSerie3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Serie 3 is 88,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "The BMW Serie 3 has a mileage of 92 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Serie 3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Serie 3 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Serie 3 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "The BMW Serie 3 has Moteur 184 cv and Puissance Fiscale 10 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.8 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Serie 3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Serie 3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/151/BMWSerie3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes GLA 200 AMG?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes GLA 200 AMG is 95,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes GLA 200 AMG?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA 200 AMG has a mileage of 104 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes GLA 200 AMG use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes GLA 200 AMG have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA 200 AMG has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes GLA 200 AMG?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA 200 AMG has Moteur 156 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes GLA 200 AMG?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.8 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes GLA 200 AMG come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes GLA 200 AMG?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Palettes au volant Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes GLA 200 AMG?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/150/MercedesGLA200."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The price of the Kia Rio is 63,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has a mileage of 41 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Kia Rio use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Kia Rio have?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has Moteur 84 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Kia Rio come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/147/KiaRio."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mini Cooper?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mini Cooper is 45,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mini Cooper?",
        "answer": "The Mini Cooper has a mileage of 101 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mini Cooper use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mini Cooper have?",
        "answer": "The Mini Cooper has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mini Cooper?",
        "answer": "The Mini Cooper has Moteur 122 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mini Cooper?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.4L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mini Cooper come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mini Cooper?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Climatisation Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Radar de recul Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mini Cooper?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/144/MiniCooper."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Fiat 500?",
        "answer": "The price of the Fiat 500 is 38,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Fiat 500?",
        "answer": "The Fiat 500 has a mileage of 99 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Fiat 500 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Fiat 500 have?",
        "answer": "The Fiat 500 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Fiat 500?",
        "answer": "The Fiat 500 has Moteur 69 cv and Puissance Fiscale 4 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Fiat 500?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Fiat 500 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Fiat 500?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Vitres électrique Toit ouvrant panoramique Climatisation."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Fiat 500?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/140/Fiat500."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 5?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 5 is 68,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 5?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 5 has a mileage of 172 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 5 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 5 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 5 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 5?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 5 has Moteur 184 cv and Puissance Fiscale 10 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 5?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6,1 L/100 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 5 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 5?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 5?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/138/BMWS%C3%A9rie5."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Peugeot 3008?",
        "answer": "The price of the Peugeot 3008 is 69,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Peugeot 3008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 3008 has a mileage of 93 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Peugeot 3008 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Peugeot 3008 have?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 3008 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Peugeot 3008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 3008 has Moteur 130 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Peugeot 3008?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Peugeot 3008 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Peugeot 3008?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Peugeot 3008?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/136/Peugeot3008."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Volkswagen Passat?",
        "answer": "The price of the Volkswagen Passat is 87,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Volkswagen Passat?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Passat has a mileage of 101 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Volkswagen Passat use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Volkswagen Passat have?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Passat has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Volkswagen Passat?",
        "answer": "The Volkswagen Passat has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Volkswagen Passat?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Volkswagen Passat come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Volkswagen Passat?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Volkswagen Passat?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/134/VolkswagenPassat."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Kia Picanto?",
        "answer": "The price of the Kia Picanto is 36,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Kia Picanto?",
        "answer": "The Kia Picanto has a mileage of 151 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Kia Picanto use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Kia Picanto have?",
        "answer": "The Kia Picanto has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Kia Picanto?",
        "answer": "The Kia Picanto has Moteur 67 cv and Puissance Fiscale 4 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Kia Picanto?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.9 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Kia Picanto come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Kia Picanto?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Port USB Rétroviseurs Electriques Jantes en alliage Vitres électrique Radar de recul Climatisation Eclairage LED Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Kia Picanto?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/129/KiaPicanto."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Fiat Punto?",
        "answer": "The price of the Fiat Punto is 28,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Fiat Punto?",
        "answer": "The Fiat Punto has a mileage of 91 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Fiat Punto use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Fiat Punto have?",
        "answer": "The Fiat Punto has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Fiat Punto?",
        "answer": "The Fiat Punto has Moteur 69 cv and Puissance Fiscale 4 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Fiat Punto?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Fiat Punto come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Fiat Punto?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Vitres électrique Climatisation."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Fiat Punto?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/126/FiatPunto."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The price of the Kia Rio is 57,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has a mileage of 40 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Kia Rio use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Kia Rio have?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "The Kia Rio has Moteur 84 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Kia Rio come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Kia Rio?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/123/KiaRio."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Seat Tarraco?",
        "answer": "The price of the Seat Tarraco is 107,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Seat Tarraco?",
        "answer": "The Seat Tarraco has a mileage of 96 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Seat Tarraco use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Seat Tarraco have?",
        "answer": "The Seat Tarraco has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Seat Tarraco?",
        "answer": "The Seat Tarraco has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Seat Tarraco?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.7L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Seat Tarraco come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Seat Tarraco?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Seat Tarraco?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/121/SeatTarraco."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Citroën C3?",
        "answer": "The price of the Citroën C3 is 34,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Citroën C3?",
        "answer": "The Citroën C3 has a mileage of 67 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Citroën C3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Citroën C3 have?",
        "answer": "The Citroën C3 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Citroën C3?",
        "answer": "The Citroën C3 has Moteur 150 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Citroën C3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.7L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Citroën C3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Citroën C3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Citroën C3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/113/CitroenC3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi Q7?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi Q7 is 285,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi Q7?",
        "answer": "The Audi Q7 has a mileage of 73 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi Q7 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi Q7 have?",
        "answer": "The Audi Q7 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi Q7?",
        "answer": "The Audi Q7 has Moteur 252 ch and Puissance Fiscale 16 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi Q7?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6 L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi Q7 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi Q7?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi Q7?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/105/AudiQ7."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Renault Megane?",
        "answer": "The price of the Renault Megane is 58,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Renault Megane?",
        "answer": "The Renault Megane has a mileage of 50 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Renault Megane use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Renault Megane have?",
        "answer": "The Renault Megane has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Renault Megane?",
        "answer": "The Renault Megane has Moteur 130 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Renault Megane?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Renault Megane come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Renault Megane?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Renault Megane?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/104/RenaultMegane."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 1 is 78,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 1 has a mileage of 75 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 1 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 1 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 1 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 1 has Moteur 136 cv and Puissance Fiscale 7 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.1 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 1 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 1?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/82/BmwSerie1."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Peugeot 308?",
        "answer": "The price of the Peugeot 308 is 43,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Peugeot 308?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 308 has a mileage of 74 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Peugeot 308 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Peugeot 308 have?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 308 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Peugeot 308?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 308 has Moteur 110 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Peugeot 308?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Peugeot 308 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Peugeot 308?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Peugeot 308?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/81/Peugeot308."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Dongfeng S50?",
        "answer": "The price of the Dongfeng S50 is 47,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Dongfeng S50?",
        "answer": "The Dongfeng S50 has a mileage of 42 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Dongfeng S50 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Dongfeng S50 have?",
        "answer": "The Dongfeng S50 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Dongfeng S50?",
        "answer": "The Dongfeng S50 has Moteur 120 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Dongfeng S50?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.9 L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Dongfeng S50 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Dongfeng S50?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Radar de recul Climatisation Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Dongfeng S50?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/79/DongfengS50."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW Série 4 is 92,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 has a mileage of 77 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW Série 4 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW Série 4 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "The BMW Série 4 has Moteur 184 cv and Puissance Fiscale 10 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.6 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW Série 4 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW Série 4?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/78/BMWserie4."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes GLA is 89,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA has a mileage of 95 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes GLA use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes GLA have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLA has Moteur 156 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.8 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes GLA come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes GLA?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/77/MercedesGLA."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The price of the Renault Clio is 43,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has a mileage of 77 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Renault Clio use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Renault Clio have?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "The Renault Clio has Moteur 90 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Renault Clio come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Renault Clio?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/76/RenaultClio."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes classe C is 92,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes classe C has a mileage of 163 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes classe C use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes classe C have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes classe C has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes classe C has Moteur 156 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.4 L / 100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes classe C come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes classe C?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/75/MercedesclasseC."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "The price of the Peugeot 2008 is 41,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 2008 has a mileage of 134 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Peugeot 2008 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Peugeot 2008 have?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 2008 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 2008 has Moteur 110 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.8 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Peugeot 2008 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Clim.automatique Bi-zone Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Peugeot 2008?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/67/Peugeot2008."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Audi Q2?",
        "answer": "The price of the Audi Q2 is 84,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Audi Q2?",
        "answer": "The Audi Q2 has a mileage of 85 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Audi Q2 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Audi Q2 have?",
        "answer": "The Audi Q2 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Audi Q2?",
        "answer": "The Audi Q2 has Moteur 116 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Audi Q2?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.2 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Audi Q2 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Audi Q2?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Audi Q2?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/64/AudiQ2."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford Fiesta is 42,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "The Ford Fiesta has a mileage of 90 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford Fiesta use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford Fiesta have?",
        "answer": "The Ford Fiesta has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "The Ford Fiesta has Moteur 116 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.2 L/100 KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford Fiesta come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/61/FordFiesta."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Chery Tiggo 3?",
        "answer": "The price of the Chery Tiggo 3 is 42,500 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Chery Tiggo 3?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 3 has a mileage of 103 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Chery Tiggo 3 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Chery Tiggo 3 have?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 3 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Chery Tiggo 3?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 3 has Moteur 126 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Chery Tiggo 3?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.7L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Chery Tiggo 3 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Chery Tiggo 3?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Chery Tiggo 3?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/59/CheryTiggo3."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes Classe A is 80,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe A has a mileage of 160 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes Classe A use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes Classe A have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe A has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes Classe A has Moteur 126 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.7L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes Classe A come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes Classe A?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/58/MercedesClasseA."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Peugeot 4008?",
        "answer": "The price of the Peugeot 4008 is 75,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Peugeot 4008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 4008 has a mileage of 82 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Peugeot 4008 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Peugeot 4008 have?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 4008 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Peugeot 4008?",
        "answer": "The Peugeot 4008 has Moteur 126 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Peugeot 4008?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.7L/100KM."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Peugeot 4008 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Peugeot 4008?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Peugeot 4008?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/56/Peugeot4008."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford Focus is 39,900 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus has a mileage of 152 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford Focus use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford Focus have?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "The Ford Focus has Moteur 125 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.7 L/100."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford Focus come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford Focus?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/51/FordFocus."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "The price of the BMW X2 is 155,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "The BMW X2 has a mileage of 31 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the BMW X2 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the BMW X2 have?",
        "answer": "The BMW X2 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "The BMW X2 has Moteur 140 cv and Puissance Fiscale 8 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.6 L/100."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the BMW X2 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of BMW X2?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about BMW X2?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/50/BMWX2."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Mercedes GLB 200?",
        "answer": "The price of the Mercedes GLB 200 is 175,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Mercedes GLB 200?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLB 200 has a mileage of 50 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Mercedes GLB 200 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Mercedes GLB 200 have?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLB 200 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Mercedes GLB 200?",
        "answer": "The Mercedes GLB 200 has Moteur 163 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Mercedes GLB 200?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 6.2 L/100 km."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Mercedes GLB 200 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Mercedes GLB 200?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Clim.automatique Bi-zone Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Toit ouvrant panoramique Android Auto Apple Car Play Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Mercedes GLB 200?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/46/MercedesGLB200amg."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "The price of the Suzuki Vitara is 62,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "The Suzuki Vitara has a mileage of 116 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Suzuki Vitara use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Suzuki Vitara have?",
        "answer": "The Suzuki Vitara has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "The Suzuki Vitara has Moteur 4 Cylindres and Puissance Fiscale 5cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7L."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Suzuki Vitara come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Suzuki Vitara?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/43/Suzuki-Vitara-35."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Chery Tiggo 2?",
        "answer": "The price of the Chery Tiggo 2 is 43,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Chery Tiggo 2?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 2 has a mileage of 75 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Chery Tiggo 2 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Chery Tiggo 2 have?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 2 has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Chery Tiggo 2?",
        "answer": "The Chery Tiggo 2 has Moteur 4 Cylindres and Puissance Fiscale 5cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Chery Tiggo 2?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 7L."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Chery Tiggo 2 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Chery Tiggo 2?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Caméra 360⁰ Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Chery Tiggo 2?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/55/CheryTiggo2."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Toyota RAV 4?",
        "answer": "The price of the Toyota RAV 4 is 144,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Toyota RAV 4?",
        "answer": "The Toyota RAV 4 has a mileage of 25 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Toyota RAV 4 use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Hybride as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Toyota RAV 4 have?",
        "answer": "The Toyota RAV 4 has a Automatique transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Toyota RAV 4?",
        "answer": "The Toyota RAV 4 has Moteur 218 cv and Puissance Fiscale 9 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Toyota RAV 4?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 4.6 L/100."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Toyota RAV 4 come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Toyota RAV 4?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Clim.automatique Bi-zone Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Toit ouvrant panoramique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Radar de recul Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Toyota RAV 4?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/54/Toyota-RAV4-Hybride."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Dacia Duster?",
        "answer": "The price of the Dacia Duster is 73,000 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Dacia Duster?",
        "answer": "The Dacia Duster has a mileage of 66 500 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Dacia Duster use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Diesel as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Dacia Duster have?",
        "answer": "The Dacia Duster has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Dacia Duster?",
        "answer": "The Dacia Duster has Moteur 130 cv and Puissance Fiscale 6 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Dacia Duster?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.2 L/100."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Dacia Duster come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Dacia Duster?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Caméra de recul Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Régulateur de vitesse Limiteur de vitesse Rétroviseurs Electriques Ecran tactile Eclairage LED Radar de recul Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Dacia Duster?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/53/DaciaDuster4X4."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the price of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "The price of the Ford Fiesta is 36,800 DT."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mileage of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "The Ford Fiesta has a mileage of 158 000 Km."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fuel does the Ford Fiesta use?",
        "answer": "This car uses Essence as its fuel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of transmission does the Ford Fiesta have?",
        "answer": "The Ford Fiesta has a Manuelle transmission."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the engine power of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "The Ford Fiesta has Moteur 82 cv and Puissance Fiscale 5 cv."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fuel consumption of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "This car has a fuel consumption of Consommation 5.2 L/100."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Ford Fiesta come with a warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes Garantie Spark de 6 mois incluse*."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main features of Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "This model includes Principaux équipements & Options Bluetooth Jantes en alliage Port USB Vitres électrique Rétroviseurs Electriques Eclairage LED Climatisation Voir plus +."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I see more details about Ford Fiesta?",
        "answer": "You can see more details at this link: https://sparkauto.tn/listing-detail/52/FordFiesta."
    }
]
